Narrator: 2
Verb first
Narrator: 1
Speaker: £150 for a T-shirt? That’s a complete rip-off!
Narrator: 2
Speaker: After insisting he could negotiate a new deal, he was forced into a climbdown.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: After ten years out of the sport, he’s made an amazing comeback and reached the final.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: After years of research into a cure for the disease, they have finally had a breakthrough.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: Family break-ups increase the risk of childhood depression.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: I find musicals a bit of a turn-off. They’re just not my cup of tea.
Narrator: 7
Speaker: I’m afraid there’s been a bit of a mix-up. I think I’ve got your case and you’ve got mine.
Narrator: 8
Speaker: I’ve only been in the job a couple of weeks, so I still don’t really know the set-up.
Narrator: 9
Speaker: It was a bit of a let-down when my friends cancelled at the last minute.
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Nobody was hurt in the accident, but my car’s a complete write-off.
Narrator: 11
Speaker: The police called for backup when they were unable to cope with the violent crowd.
Narrator: 12
Speaker: She pretended she liked her present, but her expression was a real giveaway.
Narrator: 13
Speaker: Sorry, we’re going to be about 20 minutes late. There’s a hold-up on the motorway.
Narrator: 14
Speaker: There was a really good turnout for the march – over 50,000 people.
Narrator: 15
Speaker: The shop’s had a makeover and it’s now much more modern.
Narrator: 16
Speaker: The team suffered a major setback when their captain was injured.
Narrator: 17
Speaker: There has been a breakdown in communication between the government and the unions.
Narrator: 18
Speaker: We chose the restaurant because it had a really good write-up on Tripadvisor.
Narrator: 19
Speaker: We’re just waiting to be given the go-ahead before we start working on the new project.
Narrator: 20
Speaker: We’re on standby for the evening flight – let’s hope there are some free seats.
Narrator: 21
Speaker: When my boss saw the sales figures, she had a complete meltdown and started shouting at us.